STAN CHAO

(604) 700-5765 | Vancouver, BC cardioforcake.dev@gmail.com https://stanchao.netlify.app/

Summary

I'm a recent graduate of a full-stack software engineering program. I'm now looking bring to my experience from many years of working in the financial services industry and my knowledge from my education in applied mathematics to the field of software development.

Skills

❖ Critical Thinking
❖ Communication
❖ Research
❖ Creativity

Work Experience

Personal Banker | Bank of Montreal

12/2015-present

- Consistently ranked among the top 15% of investment advisors in my market
- Q3 2020, Q3 2019 and Q1 2017 internal Spotlight Award winner
- Experience with every area of retail banking, including lending and financial planning
- Excelled in cultivating relationships with clients to drive business growth
- Helped to train new personal bankers

Customer Service Representative | Bank of Montreal

04/2012-12/2015

- Consistently exceeded sales and customer service targets
- Excelled in resolving customer issues and complaints

Energy Consultant | Superior Energy

05/2009-09/2011

- Experience with cold calling and door-to-door sales
- Full commission-based compensation
- Trained new sales representatives

Education and Training

Combined Major in Economics and Statistics University of British Columbia	2013
Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly	2021
Complete Python Bootcamp Certificate Udemy.com	2021
Chartered Financial Analyst Level 1 CFA Institute	2018
Canadian Securities Course Canadian Securities Institute	2016